mikafanclub.com 2018-08-11

# Privacy Policy - Mika Fan Club

Our privacy policy describes how we use and store the data that we gather from you in order to provide our products and services. 

* * *

##  Our Commitment To Privacy 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**MikaFanClub.com is committed to your privacy, and does not sell, exchange, or release any of your individual personal information to a third party.**

###  SCOPE OF POLICY 

This Privacy Policy applies only to **MikaFanClub.com**. This privacy policy does not apply to other companies' or organizations' websites that you may link to. You should carefully review the Privacy Policy of other websites to determine how they treat personal information. 

###  INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED AND STORED 

When you browse through any web site, certain personal information about you can be collected. Like most standard web site servers we use log files. We automatically collect and temporarily store information about your visit. We use this information for statistical purposes and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. The data collected may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, domain name, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. This data is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Your IP number is visible to most of the websites that you visit. **MikaFanClub.com** may use IP numbers to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our Web site. 

**MikaFanClub.com** is hosted by **Invision Power Services**. Please see their site for their privacy information. 

###  PERSONALLY PROVIDED INFORMATION 

The only personally identifiable information about you that is collected is that which you provide on a voluntary basis. We make every effort to ensure that whatever information you provide is maintained in a secure environment. 

MikaFanClub.com will not knowingly or intentionally disclose, give, sell or transfer any personal information about our visitors, unless required for law enforcement or statute. 

###  INFORMATION USE 

We reserve the right to perform statistical analysis of user behavior and characteristics while visiting this site. We do this in order to measure interest in and use of the site. We may share this information in the aggregate with advertisers or potential advertisers. We provide only aggregate data from these analyses to third parties. Advertisers will not be able to identify any individual from the data provided. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

###  COOKIES 

A cookie is a mechanism that allows a website to record your comings and goings, usually without your knowledge or consent. MikaFanClub.com uses Google to track website usage, visitors, what pages are viewed, and obtain aggregate demographics. We can not see your personal information. 

If you do not want to accept cookies from **MikaFanClub.com** or other sites, you must set your browser software to not accept cookies. Look in the Preferences (Firefox) or Internet Options (Microsoft Internet Explorer) feature to disable cookies. 

If you disable cookies you may not be able to use certain features on the **MikaFanClub.com** website. 

###  REGISTRATION FORMS 

The **MikaFanClub.com** registration form **requires** users to provide an e-mail address and **requests** demographic information (like zip code and country). Contact information from the registration forms is used to gather aggregate demographic data. The demographic information is shared with advertisers, potential advertisers and partners on an aggregate basis only. **Individual information is never shared with any third party. MikaFanClub.com does NOT sell your email address or distribute it to any other entity.**

###  SURVEYS AND CONTESTS 

Occasionally our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. 

The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). **Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.**

**Anonymous survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Your personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties.** We provide only aggregate data to third parties. Advertisers will not be able to identify any individual from the data provided. 

###  LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES 

This site contains hyperlinks to web sites operated by parties other than MikaFanClub.com. Such hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only. MikaFanClub.com does not control such web sites, has not reviewed such websites and is not responsible for their contents. The inclusion of hyperlinks to such web sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such web sites or any association with their operators. Linking to any off-site pages is at your own risk. 

MikaFanClub.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware of this when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. **This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.**

###  SECURITY 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, **Invision Power Services (IPS)** (host for MikaFanClub.com) has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

The IPS Spam Defense Service collects data from those sites using IPS software that choose to participate in the service. The email address and IP address of the registering member is passed to the service to determine the likelihood a registering account is a spam source. 

Data from accounts determined not to be spammers are permanently deleted within 48 hours. Data from accounts determined to be spammers may be stored indefinitely to create a block list. 

###  SPECIAL NOTICE TO PARENTS AND GUARDIANS 

**MikaFanClub.com** does not intentionally seek personal information about minors who visit this web site and encourages you to ask your children to seek your permission before providing information about themselves or their family over the Internet. 

###  SPECIAL NOTICE TO CHILDREN 

**IF YOU ARE UNDER 18 YEARS OLD, PLEASE HAVE YOUR PARENT/GUARDIAN READ THIS POLICY COMPLETELY. PLEASE ASK YOUR PARENT/GUARDIAN TO EXPLAIN IT TO YOU IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS. Ask your parent or guardian for permission before you send any personal information over the Internet.**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

###  DISCLOSURE EXCEPTIONS 

Notwithstanding the above policies, MikaFanClub.com reserves the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third parties if required to do so by law or if MikaFanClub.com believes that such action is necessary: 

* To comply with legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order; 

* To protect the MFC's rights and property; 

* To investigate reports of users sending material using a false e-mail address or users sending harassing, threatening or abusive messages; 

* To protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the MikaFanClub.com website; or 

* During emergencies, such as when MikaFanClub.com reasonably believes someone's physical safety is at risk. 

###  DATA ACCESS 

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by emailing or otherwise contacting MikaFanClub.com. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**CONTACTING US**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at mfcregister@gmail.com. All policies of Invision Power Services, Inc., our host, are governed under the laws of the United States of America and the laws of the Commonwealth of Virginia. 

This Privacy Policy was last modified on May 30, 2018.
